[{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980337068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":23096,"timeElapsed":145620},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980355553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":18482,"timeElapsed":164105},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":16715,"timeElapsed":180822},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980381471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":9198,"timeElapsed":190022},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":15532,"timeElapsed":205557},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8131,"timeElapsed":213690},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980414656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":9515,"timeElapsed":223208},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":8781,"timeElapsed":231992},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4280,"timeElapsed":236275},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":22900,"timeElapsed":263444},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":10998,"timeElapsed":274444},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980472843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6949,"timeElapsed":281395},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4298,"timeElapsed":285695},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5332,"timeElapsed":291029},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6049,"timeElapsed":297079},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4815,"timeElapsed":301896},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6815,"timeElapsed":308713},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4332,"timeElapsed":313047},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":18750,"timeElapsed":334015},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5265,"timeElapsed":339282},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6565,"timeElapsed":345849},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4465,"timeElapsed":350316},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8366,"timeElapsed":358683},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7449,"timeElapsed":366134},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":6681,"timeElapsed":372816},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4684,"timeElapsed":377501},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3532,"timeElapsed":381035},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":17116,"timeElapsed":400420},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3898,"timeElapsed":404320},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":11899,"timeElapsed":416220},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3099,"timeElapsed":419321},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980617769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6997,"timeElapsed":426321},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3233,"timeElapsed":429555},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5882,"timeElapsed":435438},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4315,"timeElapsed":439755},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4366,"timeElapsed":444123},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":13533,"timeElapsed":459490},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5066,"timeElapsed":464557},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":8432,"timeElapsed":472991},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5365,"timeElapsed":478358},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":10199,"timeElapsed":488559},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4215,"timeElapsed":492775},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3999,"timeElapsed":496776},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3781,"timeElapsed":500559},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3416,"timeElapsed":503976},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":11332,"timeElapsed":517210},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3332,"timeElapsed":520544},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4598,"timeElapsed":525144},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3699,"timeElapsed":528845},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":7815,"timeElapsed":536662},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3365,"timeElapsed":540028},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750628,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":19150,"timeElapsed":559180},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980755012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4382,"timeElapsed":563564},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3198,"timeElapsed":566764},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3732,"timeElapsed":570497},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":11716,"timeElapsed":584015},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2898,"timeElapsed":586915},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3815,"timeElapsed":590732},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3015,"timeElapsed":593749},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":10182,"timeElapsed":603933},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5216,"timeElapsed":609150},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4399,"timeElapsed":613550},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980809948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4948,"timeElapsed":618500},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980813782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3832,"timeElapsed":622334},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980832534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":16500,"timeElapsed":641086},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7781,"timeElapsed":648869},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5515,"timeElapsed":654386},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980861972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":16133,"timeElapsed":670524},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980867226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5247,"timeElapsed":675778},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6301,"timeElapsed":682085},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5731,"timeElapsed":687821},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":5599,"timeElapsed":693423},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3449,"timeElapsed":696874},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":43851,"timeElapsed":742531},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":746182},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980950564,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":12932,"timeElapsed":759116},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8849,"timeElapsed":767967},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2949,"timeElapsed":770917},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980972699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":10332,"timeElapsed":781251},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980976250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3549,"timeElapsed":784801},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980980167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3915,"timeElapsed":788719},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980983800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":792352},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980987417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3615,"timeElapsed":795969},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981014986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":25784,"timeElapsed":823538},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981017736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2748,"timeElapsed":826288},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981026520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8782,"timeElapsed":835072},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981030170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":838722},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981036271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6099,"timeElapsed":844823},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981045721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":9449,"timeElapsed":854273},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981049922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4199,"timeElapsed":858474},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981060940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":11016,"timeElapsed":869492},{"subjectID":"6q133ydebs","prolificID":"6737fba7338fc96e45b00b48","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24bfab7fba5824c5509","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981064690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3748,"timeElapsed":873242}]